

# Oksana Kravchenko

**Phone number:** +48791350961

Email: kravchenko.oksanna@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/oksana-kravchenko-a10461252/

Portfolio: https://github.com/KravchenkoOksanna/Portfolio.git

**Age:** 26

City: Krakow/Ready to relocate

Employment options: office/remote

# **Summary**

Trainee QA engineer. I have a good understanding of QC processes, requirements, methodology, and tools. Good knowledge and understanding of different types of tests (regression, functional, load, etc). Experience in writing/creating test documentation (test cases, checklists, test plans, bug reports). Experience with bug tracking systems, test management tools, API testing tools, Database. I have High communication, organization skills, and quick learning skills; positive, responsible, and flexible person.

#### **Technical skills**

# **Operation Systems**

Microsoft Windows

### **Tools and Technologies**

- Technical Documentation / SRS
- Jira, Trello, Mantis, Confuence
- TestRail, TestLink
- HTML/CSS
- MySQL
- Xpath
- XML
- JSON
- Selenium IDE
- Fiddler Everywhere
- Postman
- JMeter
- Git, GitHub
- SourceTree
- KDiff3

# Other

- Agile
- SCRUM
- Waterfall
- Kanban

# **Experience**

### Sales Manager | CSP TETŁAK & RADŁOWSKI SPÓŁKA KOMANDYTOWA

Cracow - July 2019 - Current

#### Responsibilities:

- selling supplies and services via phone calls;
- monitoring and reporting on own sales performance analytics weekly, monthly, and quarterly;
- responsibility for the control of the whole sales life cycle;
- achievement sales targets;
- evaluated performance against goals and implemented appropriate development plans.

### Customer Support Representative CCO Contact Center Outsourcing

Cracow - November 2017 - September 2019

#### Responsibilities:

- assistance and advice to clients through three channels of communication: phone, e-mail, live chat:
- supporting customer questions and issues, evaluating possible resolutions, and implementing best solutions;
- receiving reports of machine, program, and application faults;
- receiving complaints.

# Languages

- Ukrainian proficient
- Russian proficient
- Polish advanced
- English intermediate

### **Certifications**

o Nov 2022– May 2023

### Quality Assurance practice (ua)

Nataliia Popelyshko

o Oct 2022

#### GoIT English HTML (en)

GoIT - start your career in IT

Oct 2022

# Software testing: preparation for certification ISTQB Foundation $(\mathit{ru})$

Stepik

o Sep 2022

#### **Fundamentals of the Software Testing** (en)

OATestLab

o Sep 2022

### Fundamentals of software testing (ua)

Prometheus

o Sep 2022

### **Software testing for beginners** (ru)

Stepik

o Jun 2019

Google Analytics, SEO, Content Marketing & Webwriting (pl)

# **Education**

**Bachelor of Science - Oct 2014 - Apr 2018** PWSZ Name of Szymona Szymonowica | Poland Political Science Oct 2014 - Apr 2018

Specialization: Policy of security and crisis response

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).